reneerouleau.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy & Terms – Renée Rouleau Skin Care

We recognize that every visitor to RenéeRouleau.com (the "Site") is concerned about maintaining privacy. Therefore, it is our goal to make each visitor feel secure about accessing and using our Site. Set forth below is an explanation of what information Renée Rouleau collects through the services available on our Site, how we use that information, how you can opt out of certain uses of information we may collect, and a description of the policies we have adopted to help meet your privacy concerns.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information includes your name, address, email address, demographic information, hobbies and activities, product preferences, and the like, which you voluntarily submit to us. The Site uses this information to respond to specific inquiries and requests that you make to our Customer Care Department, provide you with service and support, and maintain the security and integrity of our systems. If you agree, we may use this information to send you product samples, sale coupons, product literature, or new product information. We also collect and store access information related to your account, including email address and password. When you make purchases from our Site, we may collect purchasing information such as product orders, shipping address(es), and credit card information. We use this information to open, maintain, administer, and service your account or membership, as well as to process, service, or enforce transactions you make through our Site.

STATISTICAL USE

We may use information about you for our own internal statistical, design, or operational purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns, and understand demographic, customer interest, purchasing, and other trends among our guests and customers. From time to time we may post surveys on our Site. The surveys may request demographic information (such as age range, gender, areas of interest, and familiarity with Renée Rouleau channels, products, and services) and customer feedback. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, and with each request you will have the choice of whether or not to disclose information. Such survey information will be used to improve the overall experience on the Site. We may use your personal information to create a convenient and easy-to-use shopping process that includes an online "shopping basket" that allows you to track selected products and proceed through purchase. Also, we may share transactional information with entities as necessary to process credit card payments or other purchasing or delivery systems. Finally, as our business develops, it may sell or buy corporate assets; in such transactions, customer information may be one of the business assets transferred. If Renée Rouleau, its Internet businesses, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired, customer information may be one of the assets transferred. We may outsource all of these tasks to third parties on a confidential basis. Additionally, any information you have given us about your demographics and personal and product preferences may be aggregated with other information to help us analyze how to better develop, market, and promote our products.

REMINDER

The Site will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want the Site to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, do not submit it.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Except as disclosed in this policy, we do not sell or disclose information that identifies our customers personally or makes it possible for other parties to contact them directly without our customers' consent unless we are required to do so by law or as disclosed to you when we request the information from you. We may disclose personal information for the following purposes: (1) to conform with the law, respond to claims, or comply with legal process served on Renée Rouleau (e.g. a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); (2) to enforce or apply our policies or agreements (including to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us); (3) to protect and defend our or our users' rights or property, the Site, our employees, customers or the public, including fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of our Site; or (4) if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

COOKIES

We may make use of "cookies" on our Site. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user's computer by a Web server based on the permissions set in a user's browser software. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from a user's computer (other than the contents of the cookie); rather, it is an identifier used by the website that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same server to identify the computer and subsequently to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of a site based on information stored on the host server. Therefore, cookies only identify the user's computer to the website, which may correlate other information, including personally identifying information, with the cookie. We use cookies to allow us to automate access and data entry functions of our Site such as to correlate online ordering information for purchases you may make while at the Site (if any), tailor the Site to your preferences or interests, or customize promotions or marketing. In addition, cookies allow us to track Site usage to determine those areas which are useful or popular and those that are not, thereby enabling us to improve and update the Site effectively. The advertisers and/or other content providers that may appear on this website may also use cookies that are not sent by the Site. Such ads or content may contain cookies that help track and target the interests of users of this website in order to present "personalized" advertisements or other messages that the user might find interesting. Renée Rouleau is not responsible for any such cookies. You may adjust your Web browser to either alert you of the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. For Internet Explorer or AOL users, click the Start button and then select Control Panel, Internet Options and the Security tab. If you click the Custom button, you will be able to see the cookie options. For Netscape users, select File, Preferences and then Advanced to view the cookie options. Be aware that if you elect not to accept cookies, the Site may not function properly or permit access.

CHILDREN

Our Site is a general audience site that is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. To respect the privacy of children and to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information on this Site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

SECURITY

We use commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain personal information to protect it from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction by any unauthorized party. We encrypt order information, including credit card numbers, using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that our customers' information is safe as it is sent over the Internet to our server. The Site restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the Internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.

ACCESS

You may view, change, or delete information in your account. Please sign in to the Site and use the form on the Your Account page to change or close your account. Once you close your account, you will not receive any promotional or marketing materials from us or any third party as described by this policy based on personal information you have provided to us through the Site.

CONTACT BY US

In order to provide service to you, the Site will send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of its website. From time to time, the Site and its affiliates may also wish to send you other messages or updates about the Site or its promotions and other activities. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from us, please send an email containing your request.

CONTACT

If you have questions about this privacy statement, the information practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, please contact us at 888-211-7560 or in Texas at 972-378-6655.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS

As your use of RenéeRouleau.com (the "Site") will indicate your acceptance of these terms, do not use the Site if you do not agree to be bound by these terms. We may periodically change the terms, so please check them from time to time, as your continued use of the Site signifies your acceptance of any changed items.

COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARK

Renée Rouleau, Inc values all aspects of its business. Accordingly, unless otherwise noted, all materials on the Site are protected, as are the copyrights, trade dress, trademarks, and/or other intellectual properties owned by Renée Rouleau or by other parties that have licensed their material to Renée Rouleau. All rights not expressly granted are reserved.

PERSONAL USE

Your use of the materials included on our Site is for informational and shopping purposes only. You agree that you will not distribute, publish, transmit, modify, display or create derivative works from or exploit the contents of this Site in any way. You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Renée Rouleau for any and all unauthorized uses you may make of any material on the Site. You acknowledge the unauthorized use of the contents could cause irreparable harm to Renée Rouleau and that in the event of an unauthorized use, Renée Rouleau shall be entitled to an injunction in addition to any other remedies available at law or in equity.

FEEDBACK AND SUBMISSIONS

You agree that you are and shall remain solely responsible for the contents of any submissions you make, and you will not submit material that is unlawful, defamatory, abusive, or obscene. You agree that you will not submit anything to the Site that will violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right(s). While we appreciate your interest in Renée Rouleau, we do not want and cannot accept any ideas you consider to be proprietary regarding designs, product technology, or other suggestions you may have developed. Consequently, any material you submit to this Site will be deemed a grant of a royalty-free non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, display, transmit, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from and distribute these materials throughout the universe in any medium and through any methods of distribution, transmission and display whether now known or hereafter devised. In addition, you warrant that all so-called "moral rights" have been waived.

PRODUCT SALES AND AVAILABILITY

All prices displayed on our Site are quoted in U.S. Dollars, and are valid and effective only in the United States. Renée Rouleau reserves the right without prior notice to discontinue or change specifications on products and services offered on this Site without incurring any obligations.

PRIVACY AND SECURITY

For an explanation of Renée Rouleau practices and policies related to the collection, use, and storage of our online customers' information, please read our Privacy Statement. For information about the security of your ordering information and credit card number while shopping on the Site, please refer to our Privacy and Security FAQs.

WARRANTY AND DISCLAIMER

Except as otherwise expressly stated with respect to our products, all contents of the Site are offered on an "as is" basis without any warranty whatsoever, either express or implied. Renée Rouleau makes no representations, express or implied, including without limitation implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. To the extent allowed by applicable law, Renée Rouleau does not make any warranties or representations regarding the use of the materials in its Site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, adequacy, usefulness, timeliness, reliability, or otherwise. Renée Rouleau does not guarantee that the functions contained in the Site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that this Site or its server will be free of viruses or other harmful components, or that defects will be corrected even if Renée Rouleau is aware of them.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

To the extent allowed by applicable law, Renée Rouleau shall not be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials on this Site or the performance of the products, even if Renée Rouleau has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

ERRORS

We endeavor to present the most recent, most accurate, and most reliable information on our Site at all times. However, there may be occasions when some of the information featured on our Site may contain incomplete data, typographical errors, or inaccuracies. Errors are wholly unintentional, and we apologize if erroneous information is reflected in price or availability of goods or services. We present our content "as is" and make no claims to its accuracy, either express or implied. We reserve the right to amend errors or to update information at any time without prior notice.

MINORS

Renée Rouleau asks that parents supervise their children while online. No information should be posted on our Site by minor children without parental consent.

JURISDICTIONAL

Any dispute arising from these terms shall be resolved exclusively in the state and federal courts of the State of Texas. Renée Rouleau makes no representation that materials in this Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you access the Site from outside the United States, be advised that the Site may contain references to products and services that are not available or are prohibited in your country.

EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES

Please keep in mind that the information on the Site is for educational purposes only. This information is not intended as a substitute for informed medical advice. If you have a particular health problem or condition, you should not rely upon the Site for either making a diagnosis or determining treatment. Instead, you should consult with your doctor or other qualified healthcare provider.
